Okay, this is it.
좋았어, 올 것이 왔군
You sure you wanna do this?
정말 후회 안할 거야?
Hello, Mrs. Ross.
안녕하세요, 로스 부인
안녕하세요, 레이첼 씨
Well, hello, Mr. Rachel.
-Whoa!
-Oh, my God!
세상에나
서둘러, 피비
빨랑 빨랑 빨랑
Come on, Phoebe, hurry!
Okay! Okay!
알았어, 알았다고
Oh, my God!
Is everybody getting married?
돌아가시겠군
다들 결혼하는 거야?
예배당에서 뛰면 안돼요
No running in the chapel.
이봐요, 당신이 뭔데...
Hey, don't you give me
any of your.. Hey!
- 얘들아
- 안녕
Why are you here?
여긴 웬일이야?
Ross and Rachel left a message.
They're getting married.
로스랑 레이첼이 결혼한다는
메시지를 남겼더라고
-Isn't that why you guys are here?
-Yes. Why else would we be here?
- 너희도 그래서 온 거 아냐?
- 물론이지
그럼 왜 왔겠어
What happened?
Did we miss it?
어떻게 된 거야
너무 늦게 왔나?
We missed it.
우리도 못 봤어
안 놓칠 수도 있었어
예배당에서 뛰었으면!
Maybe you wouldn't have
if you could run in the chapel!
I can't believe they got married.
로스랑 레이첼이
결혼을 하다니
그러게, 다시
데이트하는 줄도 몰랐어
I know! I didn't even know
they were dating.
I don't think they're as much dating
as they are...
데이트라기보다 사람처럼 생긴
보드카 병 두 개 같더라
...two bottles of vodka walking
around in human form.
This is insane.
미친 짓이야
뭐 어때
진짜 결혼식도 아닌데
What's the big deal?
It's not like it's a real marriage.
What?
뭐라고?
라스베가스에서 결혼하면
라스베가스에서만 유효하잖아
If you marry in Vegas,
you're only married in Vegas.
If you marry here,
you're married everywhere.
무슨 소리야, 라스베가스에서
결혼하면 어딜 가도 부부지
Really?
진짜?
Yeah.
그래
Oh, my God!
엄마야
Oh, well.
알 게 뭐냐
The One After Vegas
Why are we in bed together?
우리가 왜 함께 있지?
몰라
I don't know.
-Did we?
-I don't know.
- 우리 혹시...
- 몰라
Do you have any clothes on?
옷은 입고 있어?
Yes.
그래
- 진짜?
- 아니
-Really?
-No.
But we didn't have..
어쨌거나 우리...
...sex, did we?
섹스는 안 했겠지?
어젯밤 일이 잘 기억 안 나
가물가물해
I don't remember much
about last night.
It was such a blur.
I remember laughing.
I laughed a lot.
웃었던 건 기억나
배꼽 빠지게 웃었어
그럼 섹스는 안 했군
Then we didn't have sex.
Well, so, what did we do last night?
간밤에 무슨 짓을 했지?
I don't know, but I think
it was a lot of fun.
잘은 모르겠지만
정말 즐거웠어
너무 즐겁진 않았겠지?
안 그래?
Luckily, not too much fun, right?
- 아마 그럴 거야
- 다행이다
-I don't think so.
-Oh, thank God.
Oh, I mean,
we were really drunk.
엄청 퍼 마셨나봐
- 바보짓 안 해서 다행이다
- 그러게 말이야
I'm glad we didn't
do anything stupid.
Tell me about it.
방금 결혼했어요
잘 잤어, 피비?
Morning, Phoebe.
Well, my movie has been
officially canceled.
영화 촬영이
공식적으로 취소됐어
Joey, I'm so sorry.
조이, 어떡하니
이거 좀 먹을래?
You want my breakfast?
지금은 아무 것도
안 넘어갈 거 같아
Too depressed to eat.
I'll probably eat in, like,
five minutes.
5분만 있다가 줘
I'll fly home with you.
What time is your flight?
너희랑 같이 돌아가야겠다
몇 시 비행기야?
- 내 택시는 어쩌고?
- 이제 필요 없잖아
-What about my cab?
-I don't need that anymore.
You borrowed my cab.
You have to drive it back.
조이, 네가 빌려갔으니까
제자리에 갖다놔야지
I don't wanna drive back
by myself. I get lonely.
어떻게 나 혼자 돌아가
너무 외로워
How about if you come with me?
너랑 가면 되겠다
-It's a long trip.
-That would be great.
- 글쎄, 너무 멀잖아
- 재미있을 거야
얘기도 하고
게임도 하고...
We could talk and play games.
우리의 우정을 일신할 기회야
This could be our chance
to, like, renew our friendship.
Are you asking me
to have a "frienaissance"?
'우정부흥운동'이라도 하자고?
Sure?
그렇지
All right. Although, I don't think we
need one. I never stopped loving you.
좋아
내 사랑은 변함 없으니까
굳이 필요한 건 아니지만
- 얘들아
- 왔어?
So has anybody talked
to Dr. and Mrs. Geller yet?
닥터 겔러와
겔러 부인은 어디 있지?
메시지 받았어
곧 올 거야
They left me a message.
They'll be here.
Where is the waitress? I'm starving.
웨이트리스 어디 갔어
배고파 죽겠는데
It's a buffet, man.
여긴 뷔페다, 임마
Here's where I win
all my money back!
본전 뽑을 데를 찾았군
I gotta talk to you.
나랑 얘기 좀 하자
Sure.
그래, 무슨 일인데?
What's up?
Monica and I almost got married.
간밤에 모니카랑
결혼할 뻔했어
My God!
세상에, 잘됐다!
That's huge!
Wait a minute. Why wasn't I invited?
잠깐만, 근데 난
왜 초대 안 했냐?
들러리가 누군데
로스라고는 말하지 마
And who was gonna be your best man?
Don't say Ross. Do not say Ross.
I just don't think that Monica and I
are ready yet. I love her...
우린 아직 결혼할
준비가 안 됐어
모니카를 사랑하지만
...but seeing Ross and Rachel
come out of that chapel...
어제 로스랑 레이첼을 보니까
...was like a wake-up call that Monica
and I are moving so fast, you know.
정신이 번쩍 들더라
우린 진전이 너무 빨라
How do I tell her
without crushing her?
어떻게 얘기해야
상처를 안 받을까
Tell her she's not marriage material.
결혼상대가 아니라고 해
What?
뭐?
Girls say it to me all the time.
여자들한테 내가
맨날 듣는 소리야
날 믿어, 모니카가 나 같다면
안도의 한숨을 내쉴 거야
And if she's anything like me,
she's just gonna be relieved.
너무 이르다는 걸
어떻게 설명하지?
How do I tell him that it's too soon?
내가 자기를 더 이상 사랑하지
않는 줄 알고 상심이 클 텐데
He's gonna think
I don't love him anymore.
- 안 사랑하잖아
- 사랑해
-Well, you don't.
-Yes, I do.
Good. I was just testing you.
좋아, 테스트였어
-Hey.
-Oh, hi.
- 안녕
- 그래, 어서 와
베이컨 얘길 하던 중이야
We were just talking about bacon.
No, we were talking about tennis.
아니, 테니스 얘길 했어
테니스가 더 그럴 듯하잖아
Tennis is more believable.
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Thank you.
고마워
커피
Coffee.
What?
왜?
어젯밤 일에 대해
얘기 좀 해볼까?
Are we gonna talk about
what you guys did last night?
What do you mean "last night"?
Nothing happened last night.
어젯밤 일이라니
아무 일도 없었잖아
Ross invited us all to watch.
로스가 우릴 모두
초대했었는데?
What is the matter with you?
너 어디 아프냐?
We weren't gonna miss
our friends getting married.
레이첼, 친구 결혼식을
놓칠 순 없잖아
누가 결혼했는데?
Who got married?
You did.
너희들
What?
뭐?
우리가 언제 결혼했어
-Hello. We didn't get married.
-No, we didn't. That's ridi..
결혼이라니 말도 안 돼
Wait, wait, wait.
I remember being in a chapel.
잠깐, 예배당에 간 건
기억나는데...
They would not let us get married
when we were that drunk.
엉망으로 취한 사람을
결혼시키면 어떡해
They let you get married.
취했다고 결혼 못하나?
Most people who marry
in Vegas are drunk.
라스베가스에선 죄다
취한 상태로 결혼해
나도 지금 취했어
Now, I'm drunk right now.
I can't have a mimosa with breakfast?
I'm on vacation.
난 아침에 미모사 먹으면 안 돼?
휴가 중이잖아
What are you gonna do?
어떡할 거야
이혼전문 변호사를
찾아봐야겠지?
Well, I guess we find
a divorce lawyer.
내 생각이지만 로스는
아는 사람이 있을 거야
Well, I think.. I think
Ross already has one.
Yeah, that guy's finally gonna
be able to put in that pool.
맞아, 그 사람 드디어
수영장 만들 수 있겠다
그래, 알았어
Okay.
처음 두 번은 돈 줬으니까
세 번째는 공짜로 해주겠지?
Now, this one's free, right?
Because you paid for the first two.
Laugh it up, but the joke's on you...
맘껏 웃으셔, 안 됐지만
우린 이혼할 필요 없어
...because we don't need
to get divorced.
혼인무효선언만 하면 돼
-We're just gonna get an annulment.
-An annulment?
무효선언?
로스, 지금 수술이
해결책이 되냐?
Ross, I don't think surgery
is the answer here.
그거 네 장기잖아
Oh, that's your thing!
What?
뭐?
네 특기 말이야
매번 이혼하는 남자
Your thing. You're the guy
who gets divorced.
그래, 맞아
특기라니 말도 안 돼
No, no, that's not "my thing."
I do not love getting divorced.
나도 이혼은 싫어
싫긴 뭐가 싫어
이게 세 번째잖아
Yes, you do. This is
your third divorce.
You love divorce so much,
you're probably gonna marry it...
그렇게 이혼이 좋으면
이혼이랑 결혼해라
그것도 잘 안 되면 이혼이랑
또 이혼하든지, 이혼쟁이야
...and then it won't work out,
so you're gonna have to divorce it.
I'm so drunk.
너무 취한다
-You wanna play some Pai Gow?
-Maybe.
우리 '파이 가우'나 할까?
그래
But I kind of think we should talk
about last night.
어젯밤 얘기부터
하는 게 좋겠어
That's a good idea.
I wanna talk about last night too...
좋은 생각이야
나도 그 얘길 하고 싶었거든
-and I don't know what Pai Gow is.
-I see.
그리고 난 파이 가우가
뭔지도 몰라
그래
-So what should we do?
-I don't know.
- 넌 어떻게 하면 좋겠어?
- 글쎄
I know I love you.
하지만 널 사랑해
나도 널 사랑해
Where are we on the whole
"going back...
우리 결혼문제를 어떻게
끌고 가야 될까? 사랑해
to where they have the marriages"
thing? I love you.
That's a good question.
좋은 질문이야
어젯밤엔 주사위로 결정했잖아
다시 운명에 맡겨 보자, 사랑해
Last night we let the dice decide.
We should leave it
up to fate again. I love you!
We don't get married
unless there's a sign.
계시가 없다면
결혼 안 하는 거야
So say...
됐지? 어디 보자...
이번에도 8이 나오면
명백한 계시니까
you roll another eight,
then there's a sign...
that we should marry.
결혼하는 거야
Eight we get married...
좋아, 8이 나오면 결혼하고
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9,
10, 11, 12가 나오면
but 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10,
11, 12, we don't get married.
안 하는 거야
- 좋았어
- 그래
Sounds great.
어서 오세요
돈을 거시죠
Hey, we got a shooter.
Money, please.
-Ready?
-Ready.
- 준비됐어?
- 그래
Come on, eight.
나와라 8
그래, 8이야
Yes, yes, eight.
Eight, easy eight.
이지 8입니다
- 또 8이 나오다니
- 이래도 되는 거야?
-I can't believe I rolled an eight.
-That was so unlikely.
결혼하자고, 그래야지?
Let's get married.
I guess.
잠깐
Last night I rolled a hard eight.
저건 하드 8이 아냐
어제는 하드 8이었어
맞아, 다른 8이지
결혼은 없어, 젠장!
It was the wrong kind of eight.
No wedding! Damn it!
정말 하고 싶었는데
I wanted it so bad!
Wanna go pack?
- 짐이나 쌀까?
- 그래
옳은 일을 한 거지?
We're doing the right thing.
물론이지
Of course we are.
운명에 맡겼잖아
We left it up to fate.
If we were supposed to get married,
there would be a sign.
우리가 결혼해야 한다면
분명한 계시가 있었겠지
Okay, you have 19 questions left.
Use them wisely.
좋아, 질문이 19개
남았으니까 잘 쓰라고
Come on, Joey. You can't win
if you don't ask any questions!
어서, 조이
질문을 안 하면 이길 수...
없잖아!
-What?
-You promised me a fun road trip.
뭐야
재미있을 거라고 해놓고
We've been on the road for 6 hours,
and you've been asleep for 5 and a half.
6시간 전에 나왔는데
5시간 30분을 자니?
We are switching, and
you are going to drive back.
다음 휴게소에서 교대하고
도착할 때까지 네가 운전해
벌이라고 생각하고!
That will be your punishment,
you greedy sleeper!
이 탐욕스런 잠퉁이야
All right.
그래, 알았어
And until then, you are going
to sing to me...
그리고 노래도 불러줘야 돼
...because the radio's broken and you are
selfish, but you have a nice voice.
라디오가 고장났고 네가 이기적이긴
해도 목소리는 꽤 좋으니까
-Really?
-Sing!
- 저기, 난...
- 불러!
I wanna rock 'n' roll all night
밤새도록 춤추고
노래하겠네
징하게도 멀다
Man, this is a long drive.
Are my eyes open?
나 눈뜨고 있냐?
No!
아니!
Morning.
잘 잤어요?
-Hey.
-Hey, hubby.
안녕
당신 왔어요?
전에 얘기했던
그 혼인무효선언 말인데
Actually, I wanted to talk to you
about that whole annulment thing.
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
나 그거 안 할래
Okay.
좋아
So we'll just stay married.
그럼 이제 우린 부부네?
Yes, exactly.
바로 그거야
And I will make everyone
call me Mrs. Geller.
난 졸지에 겔러 부인이 됐고
Wow, this is so amazing.
정말 뜻밖이다
I really thought I'd have to
talk you into this more.
그렇게 쉽게 수긍을 하다니
Now I'm scared because I don't
actually think you're kidding.
그래, 농담이 아닌 것 같아서
진짜 무서워진다
I'm not kidding.
농담 아냐
난 어쨌거나...
Look...
...I can't have three
failed marriages.
결혼을 세 번씩이나
말아먹을 순 없어, 안 되지
I can't, okay?
그런 놈이 되긴 싫다고
I am not gonna be that guy.
알았어?
그건 내 특기가 아냐
Okay? No, no. That is not gonna be
"my thing."
So, what, we just
stay married forever?
그럼 우린 영원히 부부라고?
I don't know.
모르겠어
I mean, I haven't worked it all
out yet, but....
아직 생각이 다
정리된 건 아니지만
Okay, I know it's a bit crazy..
- 물론 약간은 미친 짓이지
- 그럼
달라질 게 있나? 진짜로!
How is this going
to affect you, really?
가끔 양식 같은 거 작성할 때
I mean, you fill some form out
once in a while...
instead of checking the box "Miss,"
you check the box that says, "Mrs."
'미혼' 대신 '기혼' 칸에
체크만 하면 되잖아
It's right next to it.
바로 옆에 딱 붙어있어
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right.
You know what?
그래, 네 말이 맞아
부부가 될 수도 있겠다
We can stay married...
난 미혼과 기혼 칸이 꽤 멀리
떨어져 있는 줄 알았거든
because I thought that the boxes
were far away from each other.
-No, they're right..
-Ross!
- 아냐, 바로 옆에...
- 로스!
All right.
Just...
좋아, 잠깐만 진정하고
please take a moment here...
and think about what
you're asking of me. Okay?
지금 나한테 뭘
요구하고 있는지 생각해봐
내 부탁을 들어달라고
요구하는 거야
I am asking you to do me a favor.
You are asking me to be your wife.
날 더러 네 아내가
돼달라는 요구잖아
내 아내로서 이 부탁은
들어주는 게 옳을 거야
And as my wife, I think
you should grant me this favor.
We did make vows.
서약도 했잖아
That kid kicked me really hard.
꼬마 녀석이 날 걷어차다니
Well, you did pull his hair.
자기가 머리채를 잡아당겼잖아
-He took my snack.
-I'm not getting into this again.
- 내 과자를 뺏어먹었어
- 또 시작하자고?
알았어
어쨌거나 너무 아프다
All right, you know what?
Hurts really bad.
Well, I told you not to walk. Here.
그러게 걷지 말랬잖아
이리 와봐, 됐어
There. There. Okay.
-This doesn't mean anything, does it?
-No.
- 이건 괜찮겠지?
- 그럼
낯선 사람을 태우면 어떡해
How could you pick up a hitchhiker?
He could be a rap.. He could be
a rapist or a killer or something.
강간범이나...
강간범이나
살인범일 수도 있잖아
태우기 전에
물어볼 걸 그랬나?
Don't you think I asked him that
before he got in?
너한테 그런 거 아니니까
넌 잠이나 자
I'm not talking to you.
You go back to sleep.
-And, you, are you a rapist?
-No.
- 아저씨 강간범이에요?
- 아뇨
자동차 게임 좋아해요?
Do you like car games?
Yeah, you know
the license plate game?
네, 번호판 게임 알아요?
번호판 게임 좋죠
I love the license plate game!
I'll play. I'll play.
나도 할래
No, you need your sleep.
Night-night.
안 돼, 넌 자야지
주무세요, 안녕
- 나야
- 그래
Listen. I know you wanted
to talk to me...
들어봐
내게 할말이 있겠지만
but I have an idea that may
make you wanna stay married.
이 얘기를 들으면 아마
부부로 남고 싶을 거야
We register...
혼인신고만 하면
선물은 몽땅 너 줄게
and you get to keep
all the presents.
No, Ross, come on. No, listen.
안 돼, 로스
잠깐 앉아봐
I've thought about
how to tell you this.
어떻게 설명할까 고민하다
I came up with an analogy
about a little goldfish...
얼어붙은 겨울 연못에 사는
금붕어 얘기가 생각났지만
in a pond that freezes over
in the winter...
그건 누가 괴롭힘을 당할 때
해주는 얘기더라고
but I realized that was a story about
what to do when people pick on you.
So I'm gonna actually save that
for my children's book.
나중에 애들한테나 들려줘야지
- 레이첼?
- 그래
-What's up?
-Oh, sorry.
- 헤매지 말고!
- 오, 미안
어찌됐든 우리는
부부로 남을 수 없어
The bottom line, Ross...
is we cannot stay married.
-I don't know if that's true..
-Oh, but it is.
- 정말 그럴까?
- 그렇다니까
자, 이게 뭔지 알아?
Okay. You know what this is?
바로 의견 차이라고 하는 거야
This is a difference of opinion.
-When that happens in a marriage..
-Ross, come on!
부부간에 그런 일이 생기면...
제발! 이건 결혼이 아니라
사상 최악의 숙취일 뿐이야
This is not a marriage!
This is the world's worst hangover!
Ross, listen, if you do not
get this annulment, I will.
네가 무효선언 안 하면
나라도 하겠어
All right.
All right, I'll do it.
좋아
알았어, 할게
Thank you.
고마워
Hey, hey...
저기...
혹시 혼인무효
축하파티 같은 건 없나?
is there any such thing
as an annulment shower?
There's the train station.
This is where I get off.
잠깐, 저 기차역에서
내려주세요
I have your address
and phone number.
아가씨 주소랑
전화번호는 아니까...
난 그쪽 이름하고
떠돌이라는 사실을 알죠
I have your name and the fact
that you're a drifter.
So ball's pretty much
in your court.
그러니까 알아서 하세요
All right. See you, Phoebe.
또 봐요, 피비
Come on, Phoebe, I can't
take this anymore.
피비, 우리 이러지 말자
제발 뭐라고 좀 해봐
Please talk to me.
Let me make it up to you.
내가 어떡하면 되겠니
Ground control to Major Tom
관제탑이 탐 소령에게
카운트다운 개시
엔진 점화
Commencing countdown
Engines on
Take your protein pills
영양제를 삼키고
헬멧을 써라
And put your helmet on
-This is..
-Stop it! Stop it! No!
됐어, 알았으니까 그만!
That's not fair. You know I can't
resist that beautiful voice.
그 아름다운 목소리에
저항할 수 없단 말이야
Phoebe, look, I am so sorry.
피비, 정말 미안해
I promised you a fun
road trip with your friend...
즐거운 여행을 약속했는데
그걸 지키지 못했다
and I didn't deliver, okay?
하지만 잠을 안 자는 것도
우정의 일부 아니겠어?
Now I know that you think being awake
is an important part of friendship.
네가 원한다면 눈 부릅뜨고
안 자도록 노력해볼게
So I will strive to stay awake
for as long as I know you.
그래도 밤엔 자야지
You can still sleep
at night and stuff.
Thank you.
고맙다
So can we play 20 Questions now?
우리 스무고개 다시 할까?
I got a good one.
I thought about it since Kansas.
캔자스 지날 때부터
생각해둔 게 있거든
Okay.
좋아
Is it...
뜨거운 샌드위치 비슷한 거니?
a kind of hot sandwich?
그래
Yes.
Is it a meatball sub?
미트볼 서브 아냐?
That is incredible!
이거 놀라운데?
You are the master!
네가 왕 해라
꺅! 벌레다!
Bug!
-Enough already!
-Well, you didn't have to catch them!
- 진짜 심하다
- 그걸 꼭 받아야 했어?
-You look like you're..
-Don't say it!
재미있다, 이건 꼭...
말하지 마
생각도 하지 마
Don't even think it.
알았다
All right.
Chandler, enjoy your handful.
챈들러, 삼가 애도를 표한다
Should we just get married?
그냥 결혼하는 게 어때
계시는 이 정도면 충분하잖아
All the signs are telling us to do it.
I'm sick of the signs.
이젠 지겹다
난 지금 이대로가 좋아
-I'm happy the way things are.
-Me too.
동감이야
- 난 변화가 싫어, 넌?
- 나도
-I don't want change, do you?
-No.
그럼 됐네
Then nothing changes!
Everything stays the same!
변할 건 아무 것도 없어
그냥 이대로 사는 거야
Go unpack. It's been three days,
and it drives me insane!
짐 풀어, 사흘이나 지났잖아
나 미치기 일보 직전이라고
진정해라
우리가 결혼이라도...
Jeez, relax, it's not
like we're mar..
You know, I was thinking,
what if I...
생각해봤는데 내 짐을
여기다 풀면 어떨까?
unpack here?
All your stuff would be here.
그럼 네 물건이
다 여기 있겠네
Well...
그러니까...
...what if all my stuff was here?
내 물건이 다 여기 있으면
어떻게 되지?
Then you'd be going back
and forth all the time.
그럼 매번 여길
들락거려야겠지
Doesn't make any sense.
그럴 필요가 있나?
Okay.
좋아
What if we live together,
and you get what I'm saying?
같이 살자고 하면
이해가 되겠냐?
Live together?
같이 살아?
There've been no signs for that.
그런 계시는 없었는데?
Me asking is kind of a sign.
내가 물어보는 게
일종의 계시야
Yes! Yes! Yes!
- 좋아!
- 그래!
좋아
Okay. Okay, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
잠깐, 잠깐만
Here's your key. Here's your key.
이건 집 열쇠
열쇠야, 나가서 한번 써봐
Now go out and christen it!
Go out and come back in!
나갔다가 다시 들어와
Door hasn't been locked
in five years, but okay.
5년 동안 잠긴 적이 없는
문이지만 아무렴 어때
-Ready?
-Ready!
- 됐어?
- 그래
The key broke in the lock,
and I can't get in.
열쇠가 부러져서
못 들어가겠다
Wait. Oh, my God, I can't get out!
뭐?
나도 못 나가겠어
-This isn't a sign!
-No, it's a very old key!
이건 계시가 아니겠지?
당연히 아니지
열쇠가 오래돼서 그래
- 오래돼서 그렇지?
- 맞아, 오래됐어
-It's an old key!
-Oh, my God, it's old!
I love you.
사랑해
나도 사랑해
Are you hugging the door right now?
너도 문 껴안고 있니?
No.
아니
Yeah, yeah, me neither.
그래, 나도 아냐
나 왔어
So did everything go all right
with the annulment?
혼인무효신고는 잘 끝났어?
Oh, yeah. No problems.
It's all taken care of.
그럼, 당연하지
깨끗이 해결했어
Ross, thank you.
로스, 고마워
너희들 영화 보러 갈래?
Do you wanna go see a movie?
그래, 좋지
-Yeah, why not?
-Phoebe?
피비는?
난 됐어
벌써 하나 봤거든
No, thanks.
I've already seen one.
Okay, I'm gonna get my sweater.
- 나 스웨터 입고 올게
- 그래
You wanna hear something weird?
재미있는 얘기 듣고 싶니?
Always.
두말하면 잔소리
I didn't get the annulment.
나 혼인무효신고 안 했다
What?
뭐?
우린 아직 부부야
We're still married.
Don't tell Rachel. See you later.
레이첼한텐 비밀이야
나중에 보자
코트니와 데이빗의
결혼을 축하하며
What are you doing?
뭐하냐?
Key is stuck in the lock.
열쇠가 부러져서 안 빠져
내가 고쳐줄게, 기다려
I can fix it. Hold on.
Watch out, watch out.
비켜봐
It still doesn't work.
그래도 안 되는데?
아직 안 끝났어
I'm not finished.
Nice job, Joe.
You're quite the craftsman!
잘했다, 조이
진정한 장인정신이야